A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.35 (A2010) FA495
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.35 (A2010)
1986-2009
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation
FA495
27.51 Cubic Feet 21 standard record storage boxes, R3904-R3924.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Project files transferred to the RAC by Rockefeller Foundation, 2010.
Conditions Governing Access
Records more than 10 years old are open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Separated Materials
Special Formats (digital media, audio, video) have been separated from the body of the collection. All pertinent items are assigned a unique separation number, as noted. Requests to access open special formats should reference the unique separation number.
Arrangement
Records are primarily arranged by Program, with some materials arranged by the RF traditional series numbers.
Records are arranged as received. Within folders, materials are primarily arranged in reverse chronological order.
Scope and Contents
Gramt administration files and related material.
- AC.2010.029: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1990-2005; AC.2010.029; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 standard record storage boxes, R3904-R3905.
  - Arts and Humanities (AH), AC.2010.029.1; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - AH 9923 - STANFORD UNIVERSITY - INTERCOLLEGIATE CENTER FOR CLASSICAL STUDIES - FELLOWSHIP PROGRAM, 1993-2004 (Box R3904)
    - AH 9957 - CENTER FOR TRANSCULTURAL STUDIES - PROGRAM EXPLORING CULTURAL DIMENSIONS OF GLOBALIZATION, 1997-2005 (Box R3904)
  - African Initiatives (AI), AC.2010.029.2; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - AI 9809 - UNIVERSITY OF CAPE TOWN (SOUTH AFRICA) - SUB-SAHARAN UNIVERSITIES POSTGRADUATE PROGRAM IN SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING, 1993-2003 (Box R3904)
  - Agricultural Sciences (AS), AC.2010.029.3; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - AS 9130 - STRENGTHENING FOOD PRODUCTION SYSTEMS IN AFRICA - POST-GRADUATE EDUCATION AND TRAINING FORUM, 1990-1996 (Box R3904)
    - AS 9945 - CORNELL UNIVERSITY - RESEARCH EXTENSION PROJECT, SYSTEM OF RICE INTENSIFICATION IN MADAGASCAR, 1999-2004 (Box R3904)
  - Equal Opportunity (EO), AC.2010.029.4; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - EO 9743 - BROOKINGS INSTITUTION - NATIONAL COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT POLICY ANALYSIS NETWORK, 1995-2003 (Box R3904)
    - EO 9806 - JOHNS HOPKINS UNIVERSITY - IMPLICATIONS OF WELFARE REFORM FOR LOW-INCOME HOUSING RESIDENTS, 1997-2003 (Box R3904)
    - EO 9842 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - EMPLOYMENT PIPELINES FROM POOR NEIGHBORHOODS, 1998-2003 (Box R3905)
  - Global Environment (GE), AC.2010.029.5; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - GE 9809 - CALIFORNIA - PARKS AND RECREATION (DEPT. OF) - STREAMFLOW STATION ON BULL CREEK, 1998-2003 (Box R3905)
    - GE 9901 - UNIVERSITY OF THE WEST INDIES (JAMAICA) - GRADUATE PROGRAM IN ENVIRONMENT, 1998-2004 (Box R3905)
  - Global Philanthropy (GP), AC.2010.029.6; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - GP 9939 - RESILIENCE ALLIANCE (CANADA) - INTEGRATIVE EXPERIMENTS FOR SUSTAINABILITY, 1999-2003 (Box R3905)
  - International Security (IS), AC.2010.029.7; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - IS 9910 - CENTER FOR NATIONAL POLICY - U.S. NATIONAL INTERESTS WITH RESPECT TO NORTH KOREA, 1999-2004 (Box R3905)
  - Population Sciences (PS), AC.2010.029.8
    - PS 9906 - JOHNS HOPKINS UNIVERSITY - NAFIS SADIK LEADERSHIP FELLOWS PROGRAM, 1999-2003 (Box R3905)
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2010.029.9; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - RF 92071 - AFRICAN PUBLISHING, 1991-1997 (Box R3905)
    - RF 93022 #234 - TAMIL NADU AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY --BIOTECHNOLOGY CAREER FELLOWSHIP FOR RETHINASAMY VELAZHAHAN, 1999-2004 (Box R3905)
    - RF 93022 #237 - CCS HARYANA AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (INDIA) - BIOTECHNOLOGY CAREER FELLOWSHIP FOR RAJINDER K. JAIN, 1997-2004 (Box R3905)
    - RF 93063 #79 - JIWAJI UNIVERSITY (INDIA) - ANTIFERTILITY EFFECTS OF IMMUNIZATION WITH RSMP-TT, 1995-2005 (Box R3905)
- AC.2010.034: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1994-2004; AC.2010.034; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 standard record storage box, R3906.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2010.034.1; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - RF 94010 #555 - UNIVERSITY OF GEORGIA - RESIDENT FELLOWSHIPS AT WOMANIST STUDIES CONSORTIUM (INSTITUTE FOR AFRICAN-AMERICAN STUDIES), 1994-2003 (Box R3906)
    - RF 94025 #24 - WORLD HEALTH ORGANIZATION (SWITZERLAND) - CAREER DEVELOPMENT FELLOWSHIP PROGRAM, 1995-2003 (Box R3906)
    - RF 95001 #378 - KASETSART UNIVERSITY (THAILAND) - SUBMERGENCE TOLERANCE IN RICE FELLOWSHIP, 1995-2005 (Box R3906)
    - RF 95022 #642 - KANKPEYENG, BENJAMIN W. - ADIA: ARCHAEOLOGY OF KPALEWOGU IN NORTHERN GHANA, 1997-2004 (Box R3906)
    - RF 96003 #576 - COLUMBIA UNIVERSITY - RESIDENT FELLOWSHIPS (ORAL HISTORY RESEARCH OFFICE), 1996-2000 (Box R3906)
    - RF 96003 #579 - NEW YORK UNIVERSITY - RESIDENT FELLOWS, "THE PRIVATIZATION OF CULTURE", 1997-2004 (Box R3906)
- AC.2010.038: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1989-2003; AC.2010.038; 5.24 Cubic Feet 4 standard record storage boxes, R3907-R3910.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2010.038.1; 5.24 Cubic Feet 4 record storage boxes
    - RF 96012 #13 - BANZA BAYA - CHILD MORTALllY AND FAMILY PREFERENCESIN BURKINA FASO, 1997-2003 (Box R3907)
    - RF 96022 #773 - BWENGE, CHARLES M.T. - ADIA: CODESWITCHING IN POLITICAL DISCOURSE IN TANZANIA, 1997-2003 (Box R3907)
    - RF 96023 #260 - WINTER, STEPHEN - FILM, "LOVE AND HAPPINESS", 1997-2002 (Box R3907)
    - RF 96047 #115 - AUTONOMOUS UNIVERSITY OF CHAPINGO (MEXICO) - AGROECOLOGY RESEARCH AND TRAINING PROGRAMIN OAXACA, 1999-2004 (Box R3907)
    - RF 96059 - COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT INITIATIVES, 1989-2000 (Box R3907, Box R3908, Box R3909, Box R3910)
    - RF 96059 - COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT INITIATIVES - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1989-2000 (Box R3907, Box R3908, Box R3909, Box R3910)
- AC.2010.060: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1986-2009; AC.2010.060; 14.41 Cubic Feet 11 standard record storage boxes, R3911-R3921.
  - Program and Policy - Agriculture, 923; 7.86 Cubic Feet 6 record storage boxes
    - OFFICERS CHRONOLOGICAL FILES - GARY H. TOENNIESSEN (GHT), 1989-1995 (Box R3911)
    - OFFICERS CHRONOLOGICAL FILES - GARY H. TOENNIESSEN (GHT), 1986-1998 June (Box R3912)
    - OFFICERS CHRONOLOGICAL FILES - GARY H. TOENNIESSEN (GHT), 1998 July-2000 May (Box R3913)
    - OFFICERS CHRONOLOGICAL FILES - GARY H. TOENNIESSEN (GHT), 2000 June-2003 (Box R3914)
    - OFFICERS CHRONOLOGICAL FILES - GARY H. TOENNIESSEN (GHT) AND AS/FS STAFF, 1997-2002 (Box R3920)
    - OFFICERS CHRONOLOGICAL FILES - GARY H. TOENNIESSEN (GHT) AND AS/FS STAFF, 1997-2002 (Box R3921)
  - Bellagio Study and Conference Center, 120; 6.55 Cubic Feet 5 record storage boxes
    Conditions Governing Access
    Restricted - Open in 2025
    - RESIDENT (Alexander, Meena), 2002-2003 (Box R3915)
    - RESIDENT (Anandalakshmy, Subrahmanyan), 2002-2003 (Box R3915)
    - RESIDENT (Aptekar, Lewis), 2002-2003 (Box R3915)
    - RESIDENT (Arasanayagam, Jean), 2001-2006 (Box R3915)
      Restricted - Open in 2027
    - RESIDENT (Baas, Jacquelynn) (CO-RESIDENT: Jacob, Mary J.), 2002-2005 (Box R3915)
      Restricted - Open in 2026
    - RESIDENT (Babb, Florence Evelyn), 2003-2005 (Box R3915)
    - RESIDENT (Badran, Margot F.), 2002-2004 (Box R3915)
    - RESIDENT (Banerjee, Sikata), 2001-2003 (Box R3915)
    - RESIDENT (Barnes, Jim W.), 2002-2003 (Box R3915)
    - RESIDENT (Bearison, David J.), 2002-2004 (Box R3915)
    - RESIDENT (Beckert, Sven), 2002-2003 (Box R3915)
    - RESIDENT (Belag, Andrea S.), 2002-2003 (Box R3915)
    - RESIDENT (Bharucha, Rustom H.) (CO-RESIDENT: Vera, Rodolfo C.), 2002-2003 (Box R3915)
    - RESIDENT (Bloom, Michael P.), 2002-2003 (Box R3915)
    - RESIDENT (Blount, Roy A.), 2002-2009 (Box R3915)
    - RESIDENT (Boddy, Janice P.), 2002-2003 (Box R3915)
    - RESIDENT (Boritt, Gabor S.), 2002-2003 (Box R3915)
    - RESIDENT (Camarena, Cuauhtemoc) (CO-RESIDENT: Morales, Teresa), 2002-2003 (Box R3915)
    - RESIDENT (Camnitzer, Luis), 2002-2003 (Box R3915)
    - RESIDENT (Casati, Roberto) (CO-RESIDENT: Goldman, Alvin I.), 2002-2003 (Box R3915)
    - RESIDENT (Chesterman, Simon), 2002-2003 (Box R3915)
    - RESIDENT (Clark, Ian), 2002-2003 (Box R3915)
    - RESIDENT (Clore, Gerald L.), 2002-2004 (Box R3915)
    - RESIDENT (Coble, William), 2002-2003 (Box R3915)
    - RESIDENT (COOK, PHILIP JACKSON), 2002-2004 (Box R3916)
    - RESIDENT (CORN, ALFRED), 2001-2003 (Box R3916)
    - RESIDENT (CRESSY, DAVID A.), 2002-2003 (Box R3916)
    - RESIDENT (DATER, JUDY), 2002-2004 (Box R3916)
    - RESIDENT (DAWSON, MICHAEL C.) (CO-RESIDENT HANCHARD), 2002-2005 (Box R3916)
      Biographical / Historical
    - RESIDENT (Dean, Carolyn J.), 2002-2005 (Box R3916)
    - RESIDENT (Delbanco, Nicholas), 2002-2005 (Box R3916)
    - RESIDENT (DeLoache, Judy), 2002-2004 (Box R3916)
    - RESIDENT (Desai, Gaurav), 2002-2003 (Box R3916)
    - RESIDENT (Diab, Roseanne), 2002-2004 (Box R3916)
    - RESIDENT (Dobrynin, Nikolai), 2003-2004 (Box R3916)
    - RESIDENT (Dunne, Gerald V.), 2002-2004 (Box R3916)
    - RESIDENT (Eckardt, Jason K.), 2002-2003 (Box R3916)
    - RESIDENT (Fasnacht, Heide), 2000-2006 (Box R3916)
    - RESIDENT (Fennelly), 2003 (Box R3916)
    - RESIDENT (Ferrari, Gina), 2002-2003 (Box R3916)
    - RESIDENT (Fiore, Teresa), 2002-2003 (Box R3916)
    - RESIDENT (Fletcher, Robert Hilman), 2002-2003 (Box R3916)
    - RESIDENT (Foot, Rosemary J.), 2002-2003 (Box R3916)
    - RESIDENT (Frost, Elisabeth A.), 2003-2004 (Box R3916)
    - RESIDENT (Gonzalez, Anita), 2001-2003 (Box R3916)
    - RESIDENT (Greenbaum), 2001-2003 (Box R3916)
    - RESIDENT (Grobet, Lourdes), 2002-2003 (Box R3916)
    - RESIDENT (Gruman, Jessie C.), 2002-2004 (Box R3916)
    - RESIDENT (Guivant, Julia), 2002-2004 (Box R3916)
    - RESIDENT (Gunawardane), 2002-2003 (Box R3916)
    - RESIDENT (Hawes, William K.), 2002-2008 (Box R3916)
      Restricted - Open in 2029
    - RESIDENT (Hawley, John C.), 2002-2003 (Box R3916)
    - RESIDENT (Hock, Louis), 2003-2004 (Box R3917)
    - RESIDENT (Hocking, Barbara), 2002-2003 (Box R3917)
    - RESIDENT (Holstius, Karin) (CO-RESIDENT: Malaska), 2002-2004 (Box R3917)
    - RESIDENT (Howe, Daniel W.), 2002-2003 (Box R3917)
    - RESIDENT (Kinnell, Galway), 2002-2003 (Box R3917)
    - RESIDENT (Klitzman, Robert), 2002-2003 (Box R3917)
    - RESIDENT (Krasikov, Anatoly), 2002-2004 (Box R3917)
    - RESIDENT (Kuivila, Ronald J.), 2001-2004 (Box R3917)
    - RESIDENT (Kumar, Amshan), 2002-2003 (Box R3917)
    - RESIDENT (Labelle, Charles), 2002-2003 (Box R3917)
    - RESIDENT (Lanqer, Lawrence), 2002-2003 (Box R3917)
    - RESIDENT (Leibowitz, Herbert), 1998-2003 (Box R3917)
    - RESIDENT (Leonard, Zoe), 2002-2004 (Box R3917)
    - RESIDENT (Lerman, Liz), 2002-2004 (Box R3917)
    - RESIDENT (Levin, Theodore) (CO-RESIDENT: Suzukei), 2002-2006 (Box R3917)
    - RESIDENT (Lijphart, Arend), 2002-2004 (Box R3917)
    - RESIDENT (Lindsay, Arturo) (CO-RESIDENT: Moore, Opal), 2002-2003 (Box R3917)
    - RESIDENT (Link, Daniel), 2002-2003 (Box R3917)
    - RESIDENT (Lionnet, Frangoise) (CO-RESIDENT: Tranquille), 2002-2003 (Box R3917)
    - RESIDENT (Lopez, Alfred J.), 2002-2003 (Box R3917)
    - RESIDENT (Mahuad, Jamil), 2003-2004 (Box R3917)
    - RESIDENT (Manderson, Lenore), 2002-2003 (Box R3917)
    - RESIDENT (McKenna, Patricia), 2001-2003 (Box R3917)
    - RESIDENT (Mehrotra, Arvind K., 2002-2003 (Box R3917)
    - RESIDENT (Meltzer, Harold), 2002-2004 (Box R3917)
    - RESIDENT (Miller, Damian R.), 2002-2009 (Box R3918)
      Restricted - Open in 2030
    - RESIDENT (Minear, Larry), 2002-2004 (Box R3918)
    - RESIDENT (Mitra, Reshmi), 2002-2004 (Box R3918)
    - RESIDENT (Nagel, James), 2003-2004 (Box R3918)
    - RESIDENT (Naito, Akemi), 2002-2004 (Box R3918)
    - RESIDENT (Nathan, David), 2002-2003 (Box R3918)
    - RESIDENT (Ono, Hiroshi) (CO-RESIDENT: Wade, Nicholas J.), 2002-2004 (Box R3918)
    - RESIDENT (Orlandersmith), 2002-2003 (Box R3918)
    - RESIDENT (Pandey, Pramod K.), 2002-2003 (Box R3918)
    - RESIDENT (Paris, Jan), 2002-2003 (Box R3918)
    - RESIDENT (Paternosto, Cesar P.) (CO-RESIDENT: Vicuna), 2002-2004 (Box R3918)
    - RESIDENT (Pearson, Craig J.), 2001-2003 (Box R3918)
    - RESIDENT (Pedraza, Silvia), 2002-2004 (Box R3918)
    - RESIDENT (Preis-Smith, Agata), 2002-2003 (Box R3918)
    - RESIDENT (Rock, Paul E.), 2001-2004 (Box R3918)
    - RESIDENT (Rovine, Victoria L.), 2003 (Box R3918)
    - RESIDENT (Ruiz, Ramon E.), 2002-2003 (Box R3918)
    - RESIDENTI (Sajko, Ivana), 2002-2003 (Box R3918)
    - RESIDENT (Saxonhouse, Gary), 2002-2003 (Box R3918)
    - RESIDENT (Schmidt, Vivien A.), 2002-2003 (Box R3918)
    - RESIDENT (Schroeder, Steven), 2002-2004 (Box R3918)
    - RESIDENT (Segerstrale, Ullica), 2002-2004 (Box R3918)
    - RESIDENT (Siegel, Lee A.), 2003-2004 (Box R3918)
    - RESIDENT (Simons, David J.), 2002-2003 (Box R3918)
    - RESIDENT (Sloan, Richard P.), 2002-2003 (Box R3919)
    - RESIDENT (Soremekun, Kayode), 2002-2004 (Box R3919)
    - RESIDENT (Spelman, Jon), 2002-2003 (Box R3919)
    - RESIDENT (Stehr, Nico), 2002-2003 (Box R3919)
    - RESIDENT (Strauss, Sidney), 2002-2003 (Box R3919)
    - RESIDENT !Strickland, Rennard), 2002-2003 (Box R3919)
    - RESIDENT (Tanvir, Habib), 2002-2003 (Box R3919)
    - RESIDENT (Turner, Nancy Jean), 2001-2003 (Box R3919)
    - RESIDENT (Tye, Larry), 2001-2003 (Box R3919)
    - RESIDENT (Varley, Ann), 2002-2003 (Box R3919)
    - RESIDENT (Vitalis, Robert), 2002-2004 (Box R3919)
    - RESIDENT (Vujacic, Veljko), 2002-2003 (Box R3919)
    - RESIDENT (Wade, Robert), 2002-2003 (Box R3919)
    - RESIDENT (Wassertheil-Smoller), 2002-2003 (Box R3919)
    - RESIDENT (Weber, Donald), 2002-2003 (Box R3919)
    - RESIDENT (Widner, Jennifer A.), 2001-2003 (Box R3919)
    - RESIDENT (Woodson, Wendy), 2002-2003 (Box R3919)
    - RESIDENT (Woodward, David), 2002-2003 (Box R3919)
    - RESIDENT (Wright, Donald R.), 2002-2003 (Box R3919)
    - RESIDENT (Yoo, John Choon), 2002-2003 (Box R3919)
    - RESIDENT (Yuson, Alfred A.), 2003-2004 (Box R3919)
    - RESIDENT (Zuckermann, Ghil'ad), 2002-2003 (Box R3919)
- AC.2010.070: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1991-2006; AC.2010.070; 3.94 Cubic Feet 3 standard record storage boxes, R3922-R3924.
  - Bellagio Study and Conference Center, 120; 3.94 Cubic Feet 3 record storage boxes
    - CONFERENCE: Art and Science: A Meeting between Artists and Scientists on the Creative Process, 2000-2002 (Box R3922)
    - CONFERENCE: Changing Academic Workplace in International Perspective, 2000-2001 (Box R3922)
    - CONFERENCE: Consensus on the Use of Mifepristone to Reduce Unwanted Preonancies and Recourse to Abortion, 2000-2006 (Box R3922)
    - CONFERENCE: Democratization and the Mass Media: Comparative Perspectives from Europe and Asia, 1999-2002 (Box R3922)
    - CONFERENCE: Enabling Farmer Participation: New Curricula for Transforming the Innovation Paradigm, 2001 (Box R3922)
    - CONFERENCE: Examination of Issues in Evaluating Complex Social Initiatives, 2000-2002 (Box R3922)
    - CONFERENCE: Formation of the Global Equity Gauge Alliance, 2001 (Box R3922)
    - CONFERENCE: Foundation Executive Group, 1999-2001 (Box R3922)
    - CONFERENCE: Global Inequality, 2000-2001 (Box R3922)
    - CONFERENCE: Gross Domestic Product vs. Quality of Life, 1999-2004 (Box R3922)
    - CONFERENCE: Improved Management of IPR during Research and Development of Health Products, 2001 (Box R3922)
    - CONFERENCE: International Cross-Cultural Perspectives on Workforce Diversity, 2000-2002 (Box R3922)
    - CONFERENCE: Malaria Diagnostic Strategies for the 21st Century, 2000-2001 (Box R3923)
    - CONFERENCE: New Historical Syntax of Latin, 2000-2001 (Box R3923)
    - CONFERENCE: Nutrition Transition and Its Implications for Health in the Developina World, 2000-2002 (Box R3923)
    - CONFERENCE: Priorities for Health Investments in Africa, 2000-2001 (Box R3923)
    - CONFERENCE: Religion and Civil Society, 2000-2003 (Box R3923)
    - CONFERENCE: Rockefeller Foundation Board of Trustees, 2001 (Box R3923)
    - CONFERENCE: Strengthening Minority Rights Globally, 1999-2003 (Box R3923)
    - CONFERENCE: Toward a Global Strategy to Transform the Automobile, 2000-2002 (Box R3923)
    - CONFERENCE: Unfinished Business: Iran, Iraq, and the Aftermath of War, 2000-2002 (Box R3923)
    - CONFERENCE: Visual and Spatial Reasoning in Design: Computational and Cognative Approaches, 2000-2002 (Box R3923)
    - CONFERENCE: Women and Gender in the Middle East: A Multidisciplinary Assessment of Theory and Research, 2000-2002 (Box R3923)
    - CONFERENCE: Working with Men to End Gender-based Violence: An lnterchange for Global Action, 2000-2002 (Box R3923)
    - CONFERENCE: World Association of Medical Editors: Agenda for the Future, 1999-2001 (Box R3923)
    - BC TEAM: Conflicts and Potential of Integration in South Caucasus: Public and Elite Opinion, 2001 (Box R3924)
    - BC TEAM: Domestic Water Use and Environmental Health in East Africa: Three Decades after "Drawers of Water", 2000-2002 (Box R3924)
    - BC TEAM: From Pilot Projects to Policies and Programs: Strategies for Scaling up Innovations in Health Service Delivery, 2000-2002 (Box R3924)
    - BC TEAM: Future of Neo-Latin Studies in the 21st Century, 2000-2001 (Box R3924)
    - BC TEAM: International Classification for the Study of Post Chernobvl Thyroid Cancer, 2000-2001 (Box R3924)
    - BC TEAM: International Coalition of Historic Site Museums of Conscience, 2001-2002 (Box R3924)
    - BC TEAM: International Coalition of Historic Site Museums of Conscience - Lower East Side Tenement Museum - Historic Site of Conscience - VHS, 2001-2002; 2010:070:001 (Item 2010:070:001)
      Separated Materials
      VHS was separated from file.
    - BC TEAM: Manual of Epidemiology for District Health Management, 2000-2001 (Box R3924)
    - BC TEAM: Political Impact of Women's Movements in Africa, 2000-2002 (Box R3924)
    - BC TEAM: Power, Culture, Identity: Women and the Politics of Place, 2000-2001 (Box R3924)
    - BC TEAM: Scientific Results of Contaminated Zones/Regions Near Chernobyl, 2001 (Box R3924)
    - BC TEAM: Women Writing Africa: West/Sahel Regional Volume, 2000-2006 (Box R3924)